[
    {
        "question": "[36, 12, 22, 32, 21, 85]",
        "answer": "[12, 21, 22, 32, 36, 85]",
        "choices": [
            "[12, 21, 22, 32, 36, 85]",
            "[21, 22, 32, 85, 12, 36]",
            "[85, 21, 36, 12, 32, 22]",
            "[36, 12, 21, 22, 32, 85]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[57, 60, 77, 79, 47, 14]",
        "answer": "[14, 47, 57, 60, 77, 79]",
        "choices": [
            "[14, 47, 57, 60, 77, 79]",
            "[77, 14, 57, 47, 79, 60]",
            "[47, 77, 79, 60, 57, 14]",
            "[77, 79, 14, 60, 57, 47]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[78, 77, 63, 38, 91, 59]",
        "answer": "[38, 59, 63, 77, 78, 91]",
        "choices": [
            "[38, 59, 63, 77, 78, 91]",
            "[77, 38, 63, 91, 78, 59]",
            "[59, 91, 78, 38, 77, 63]",
            "[63, 59, 38, 78, 91, 77]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[76, 30, 39, 40, 95, 29]",
        "answer": "[29, 30, 39, 40, 76, 95]",
        "choices": [
            "[29, 30, 39, 40, 76, 95]",
            "[76, 40, 29, 30, 95, 39]",
            "[30, 29, 40, 39, 95, 76]",
            "[95, 30, 76, 39, 29, 40]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[87, 81, 58, 51, 42, 27]",
        "answer": "[27, 42, 51, 58, 81, 87]",
        "choices": [
            "[27, 42, 51, 58, 81, 87]",
            "[51, 27, 87, 58, 81, 42]",
            "[42, 87, 58, 51, 81, 27]",
            "[58, 27, 87, 42, 51, 81]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[27, 66, 74, 58, 22, 49]",
        "answer": "[22, 27, 49, 58, 66, 74]",
        "choices": [
            "[22, 27, 49, 58, 66, 74]",
            "[66, 27, 74, 58, 49, 22]",
            "[66, 27, 49, 74, 22, 58]",
            "[66, 49, 27, 58, 74, 22]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[12, 82, 98, 53, 62, 47]",
        "answer": "[12, 47, 53, 62, 82, 98]",
        "choices": [
            "[12, 47, 53, 62, 82, 98]",
            "[53, 82, 98, 62, 47, 12]",
            "[12, 98, 53, 82, 47, 62]",
            "[82, 53, 12, 62, 47, 98]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[49, 39, 76, 10, 98, 23]",
        "answer": "[10, 23, 39, 49, 76, 98]",
        "choices": [
            "[10, 23, 39, 49, 76, 98]",
            "[39, 98, 76, 10, 23, 49]",
            "[49, 10, 39, 23, 76, 98]",
            "[10, 49, 23, 98, 39, 76]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[25, 41, 45, 46, 61, 93]",
        "answer": "[25, 41, 45, 46, 61, 93]",
        "choices": [
            "[25, 41, 45, 46, 61, 93]",
            "[93, 61, 25, 45, 46, 41]",
            "[93, 45, 41, 61, 46, 25]",
            "[25, 45, 93, 41, 61, 46]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[30, 81, 34, 79, 77, 65]",
        "answer": "[30, 34, 65, 77, 79, 81]",
        "choices": [
            "[30, 34, 65, 77, 79, 81]",
            "[79, 77, 30, 81, 34, 65]",
            "[81, 65, 77, 79, 30, 34]",
            "[81, 30, 65, 79, 34, 77]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[87, 49, 24, 54, 67, 99]",
        "answer": "[24, 49, 54, 67, 87, 99]",
        "choices": [
            "[24, 49, 54, 67, 87, 99]",
            "[99, 87, 24, 67, 54, 49]",
            "[49, 99, 54, 24, 67, 87]",
            "[24, 87, 49, 67, 99, 54]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[95, 12, 52, 77, 84, 56]",
        "answer": "[12, 52, 56, 77, 84, 95]",
        "choices": [
            "[12, 52, 56, 77, 84, 95]",
            "[84, 12, 52, 77, 56, 95]",
            "[12, 52, 95, 56, 84, 77]",
            "[56, 52, 12, 84, 77, 95]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[91, 49, 84, 90, 59, 13]",
        "answer": "[13, 49, 59, 84, 90, 91]",
        "choices": [
            "[13, 49, 59, 84, 90, 91]",
            "[84, 59, 49, 91, 90, 13]",
            "[90, 84, 59, 13, 91, 49]",
            "[90, 91, 59, 49, 84, 13]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[78, 46, 88, 98, 36, 84]",
        "answer": "[36, 46, 78, 84, 88, 98]",
        "choices": [
            "[36, 46, 78, 84, 88, 98]",
            "[78, 46, 98, 84, 36, 88]",
            "[46, 84, 88, 36, 78, 98]",
            "[84, 98, 36, 78, 88, 46]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[36, 82, 15, 51, 62, 61]",
        "answer": "[15, 36, 51, 61, 62, 82]",
        "choices": [
            "[15, 36, 51, 61, 62, 82]",
            "[36, 51, 15, 62, 82, 61]",
            "[82, 51, 62, 36, 15, 61]",
            "[51, 36, 61, 15, 62, 82]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[22, 88, 19, 26, 25, 44]",
        "answer": "[19, 22, 25, 26, 44, 88]",
        "choices": [
            "[19, 22, 25, 26, 44, 88]",
            "[25, 22, 88, 19, 44, 26]",
            "[25, 22, 44, 26, 88, 19]",
            "[88, 22, 26, 44, 25, 19]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[19, 44, 41, 78, 84, 54]",
        "answer": "[19, 41, 44, 54, 78, 84]",
        "choices": [
            "[19, 41, 44, 54, 78, 84]",
            "[44, 78, 41, 54, 84, 19]",
            "[54, 44, 84, 19, 41, 78]",
            "[19, 84, 54, 78, 44, 41]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[59, 34, 99, 32, 68, 78]",
        "answer": "[32, 34, 59, 68, 78, 99]",
        "choices": [
            "[32, 34, 59, 68, 78, 99]",
            "[99, 34, 59, 32, 68, 78]",
            "[99, 59, 78, 68, 34, 32]",
            "[32, 78, 59, 34, 99, 68]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[88, 61, 76, 99, 56, 27]",
        "answer": "[27, 56, 61, 76, 88, 99]",
        "choices": [
            "[27, 56, 61, 76, 88, 99]",
            "[61, 99, 76, 88, 27, 56]",
            "[76, 61, 99, 27, 56, 88]",
            "[56, 99, 88, 61, 27, 76]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[76, 55, 25, 23, 81, 62]",
        "answer": "[23, 25, 55, 62, 76, 81]",
        "choices": [
            "[23, 25, 55, 62, 76, 81]",
            "[25, 23, 62, 55, 76, 81]",
            "[81, 76, 23, 62, 25, 55]",
            "[81, 55, 23, 76, 62, 25]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[11, 59, 54, 57, 17, 12]",
        "answer": "[11, 12, 17, 54, 57, 59]",
        "choices": [
            "[11, 12, 17, 54, 57, 59]",
            "[54, 12, 59, 17, 11, 57]",
            "[59, 11, 17, 12, 54, 57]",
            "[17, 59, 54, 57, 12, 11]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[75, 25, 59, 87, 10, 74]",
        "answer": "[10, 25, 59, 74, 75, 87]",
        "choices": [
            "[10, 25, 59, 74, 75, 87]",
            "[87, 25, 75, 10, 59, 74]",
            "[10, 74, 25, 59, 75, 87]",
            "[25, 87, 74, 10, 59, 75]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[14, 32, 59, 53, 78, 84]",
        "answer": "[14, 32, 53, 59, 78, 84]",
        "choices": [
            "[14, 32, 53, 59, 78, 84]",
            "[14, 84, 53, 32, 78, 59]",
            "[14, 84, 53, 78, 59, 32]",
            "[59, 53, 78, 14, 32, 84]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[17, 68, 63, 93, 42, 78]",
        "answer": "[17, 42, 63, 68, 78, 93]",
        "choices": [
            "[17, 42, 63, 68, 78, 93]",
            "[42, 63, 78, 93, 17, 68]",
            "[93, 63, 42, 78, 17, 68]",
            "[63, 17, 78, 42, 93, 68]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[67, 90, 17, 94, 18, 70]",
        "answer": "[17, 18, 67, 70, 90, 94]",
        "choices": [
            "[17, 18, 67, 70, 90, 94]",
            "[70, 17, 94, 18, 67, 90]",
            "[18, 17, 94, 70, 67, 90]",
            "[18, 70, 90, 17, 94, 67]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[28, 97, 75, 40, 34, 78]",
        "answer": "[28, 34, 40, 75, 78, 97]",
        "choices": [
            "[28, 34, 40, 75, 78, 97]",
            "[97, 40, 75, 78, 34, 28]",
            "[78, 40, 28, 34, 75, 97]",
            "[40, 75, 34, 78, 28, 97]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[72, 96, 62, 14, 66, 57]",
        "answer": "[14, 57, 62, 66, 72, 96]",
        "choices": [
            "[14, 57, 62, 66, 72, 96]",
            "[66, 57, 14, 62, 72, 96]",
            "[96, 72, 57, 66, 14, 62]",
            "[62, 96, 66, 57, 72, 14]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[20, 87, 45, 59, 27, 63]",
        "answer": "[20, 27, 45, 59, 63, 87]",
        "choices": [
            "[20, 27, 45, 59, 63, 87]",
            "[87, 45, 59, 20, 27, 63]",
            "[59, 87, 20, 63, 27, 45]",
            "[45, 20, 63, 59, 27, 87]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[62, 64, 29, 23, 17, 93]",
        "answer": "[17, 23, 29, 62, 64, 93]",
        "choices": [
            "[17, 23, 29, 62, 64, 93]",
            "[62, 64, 23, 17, 93, 29]",
            "[64, 29, 62, 23, 17, 93]",
            "[93, 64, 23, 62, 17, 29]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[25, 60, 34, 78, 85, 22]",
        "answer": "[22, 25, 34, 60, 78, 85]",
        "choices": [
            "[22, 25, 34, 60, 78, 85]",
            "[78, 85, 60, 25, 34, 22]",
            "[85, 60, 34, 22, 78, 25]",
            "[78, 60, 22, 34, 85, 25]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[74, 51, 32, 30, 29, 97]",
        "answer": "[29, 30, 32, 51, 74, 97]",
        "choices": [
            "[29, 30, 32, 51, 74, 97]",
            "[51, 29, 97, 74, 30, 32]",
            "[51, 30, 97, 74, 29, 32]",
            "[30, 29, 97, 51, 32, 74]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[18, 36, 84, 88, 20, 55]",
        "answer": "[18, 20, 36, 55, 84, 88]",
        "choices": [
            "[18, 20, 36, 55, 84, 88]",
            "[18, 88, 55, 36, 84, 20]",
            "[18, 55, 84, 88, 20, 36]",
            "[55, 88, 20, 84, 36, 18]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[86, 88, 46, 12, 83, 65]",
        "answer": "[12, 46, 65, 83, 86, 88]",
        "choices": [
            "[12, 46, 65, 83, 86, 88]",
            "[88, 65, 12, 86, 83, 46]",
            "[88, 65, 86, 83, 12, 46]",
            "[12, 88, 65, 86, 83, 46]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[100, 76, 54, 81, 14, 38]",
        "answer": "[14, 38, 54, 76, 81, 100]",
        "choices": [
            "[14, 38, 54, 76, 81, 100]",
            "[81, 54, 14, 100, 76, 38]",
            "[38, 81, 54, 14, 76, 100]",
            "[38, 81, 100, 14, 76, 54]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[90, 73, 18, 51, 46, 29]",
        "answer": "[18, 29, 46, 51, 73, 90]",
        "choices": [
            "[18, 29, 46, 51, 73, 90]",
            "[73, 90, 18, 29, 51, 46]",
            "[18, 46, 29, 73, 90, 51]",
            "[51, 90, 73, 29, 18, 46]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[66, 86, 85, 37, 78, 45]",
        "answer": "[37, 45, 66, 78, 85, 86]",
        "choices": [
            "[37, 45, 66, 78, 85, 86]",
            "[37, 86, 66, 85, 78, 45]",
            "[86, 85, 78, 37, 66, 45]",
            "[85, 66, 37, 86, 45, 78]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[11, 22, 40, 100, 91, 42]",
        "answer": "[11, 22, 40, 42, 91, 100]",
        "choices": [
            "[11, 22, 40, 42, 91, 100]",
            "[22, 42, 91, 11, 100, 40]",
            "[22, 40, 91, 11, 100, 42]",
            "[40, 100, 91, 42, 22, 11]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[26, 29, 58, 99, 16, 39]",
        "answer": "[16, 26, 29, 39, 58, 99]",
        "choices": [
            "[16, 26, 29, 39, 58, 99]",
            "[29, 26, 16, 58, 39, 99]",
            "[26, 39, 16, 29, 58, 99]",
            "[29, 16, 26, 39, 99, 58]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[39, 90, 70, 99, 62, 91]",
        "answer": "[39, 62, 70, 90, 91, 99]",
        "choices": [
            "[39, 62, 70, 90, 91, 99]",
            "[62, 39, 90, 91, 99, 70]",
            "[90, 70, 39, 62, 99, 91]",
            "[39, 90, 70, 91, 62, 99]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[82, 13, 71, 18, 86, 27]",
        "answer": "[13, 18, 27, 71, 82, 86]",
        "choices": [
            "[13, 18, 27, 71, 82, 86]",
            "[86, 13, 82, 27, 18, 71]",
            "[82, 86, 71, 27, 13, 18]",
            "[18, 13, 71, 27, 82, 86]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[21, 27, 56, 46, 18, 39]",
        "answer": "[18, 21, 27, 39, 46, 56]",
        "choices": [
            "[18, 21, 27, 39, 46, 56]",
            "[21, 18, 39, 46, 56, 27]",
            "[46, 21, 27, 39, 56, 18]",
            "[39, 21, 27, 18, 56, 46]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[14, 56, 20, 69, 74, 34]",
        "answer": "[14, 20, 34, 56, 69, 74]",
        "choices": [
            "[14, 20, 34, 56, 69, 74]",
            "[69, 34, 20, 56, 74, 14]",
            "[56, 20, 14, 34, 74, 69]",
            "[74, 69, 56, 34, 14, 20]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[88, 82, 67, 68, 15, 16]",
        "answer": "[15, 16, 67, 68, 82, 88]",
        "choices": [
            "[15, 16, 67, 68, 82, 88]",
            "[15, 16, 88, 67, 68, 82]",
            "[68, 88, 16, 15, 82, 67]",
            "[68, 15, 67, 16, 82, 88]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[98, 62, 72, 33, 74, 48]",
        "answer": "[33, 48, 62, 72, 74, 98]",
        "choices": [
            "[33, 48, 62, 72, 74, 98]",
            "[72, 62, 98, 48, 74, 33]",
            "[98, 33, 48, 72, 74, 62]",
            "[62, 74, 33, 48, 72, 98]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[56, 92, 65, 40, 42, 29]",
        "answer": "[29, 40, 42, 56, 65, 92]",
        "choices": [
            "[29, 40, 42, 56, 65, 92]",
            "[65, 29, 92, 42, 40, 56]",
            "[56, 65, 92, 42, 40, 29]",
            "[92, 56, 29, 40, 65, 42]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[51, 49, 65, 89, 47, 52]",
        "answer": "[47, 49, 51, 52, 65, 89]",
        "choices": [
            "[47, 49, 51, 52, 65, 89]",
            "[49, 65, 52, 47, 89, 51]",
            "[52, 47, 51, 89, 49, 65]",
            "[52, 89, 51, 49, 65, 47]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[75, 30, 66, 22, 90, 15]",
        "answer": "[15, 22, 30, 66, 75, 90]",
        "choices": [
            "[15, 22, 30, 66, 75, 90]",
            "[22, 15, 30, 90, 75, 66]",
            "[15, 66, 30, 75, 90, 22]",
            "[66, 90, 15, 22, 75, 30]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[38, 83, 49, 27, 81, 57]",
        "answer": "[27, 38, 49, 57, 81, 83]",
        "choices": [
            "[27, 38, 49, 57, 81, 83]",
            "[57, 49, 83, 38, 27, 81]",
            "[49, 81, 83, 38, 27, 57]",
            "[57, 81, 27, 83, 49, 38]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[94, 29, 67, 40, 50, 77]",
        "answer": "[29, 40, 50, 67, 77, 94]",
        "choices": [
            "[29, 40, 50, 67, 77, 94]",
            "[67, 77, 29, 94, 50, 40]",
            "[50, 77, 67, 94, 29, 40]",
            "[50, 40, 77, 94, 29, 67]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[13, 75, 36, 76, 40, 43]",
        "answer": "[13, 36, 40, 43, 75, 76]",
        "choices": [
            "[13, 36, 40, 43, 75, 76]",
            "[36, 75, 43, 13, 76, 40]",
            "[43, 36, 40, 75, 13, 76]",
            "[75, 13, 36, 76, 40, 43]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[20, 69, 13, 10, 59, 97]",
        "answer": "[10, 13, 20, 59, 69, 97]",
        "choices": [
            "[10, 13, 20, 59, 69, 97]",
            "[10, 13, 59, 20, 69, 97]",
            "[59, 69, 10, 20, 13, 97]",
            "[97, 10, 13, 69, 20, 59]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[43, 34, 33, 31, 32, 81]",
        "answer": "[31, 32, 33, 34, 43, 81]",
        "choices": [
            "[31, 32, 33, 34, 43, 81]",
            "[31, 81, 32, 34, 43, 33]",
            "[33, 34, 81, 32, 31, 43]",
            "[34, 33, 43, 32, 81, 31]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[43, 65, 46, 51, 64, 38]",
        "answer": "[38, 43, 46, 51, 64, 65]",
        "choices": [
            "[38, 43, 46, 51, 64, 65]",
            "[64, 38, 46, 43, 65, 51]",
            "[65, 64, 38, 51, 43, 46]",
            "[51, 46, 38, 65, 64, 43]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[10, 18, 82, 72, 24, 97]",
        "answer": "[10, 18, 24, 72, 82, 97]",
        "choices": [
            "[10, 18, 24, 72, 82, 97]",
            "[24, 72, 82, 18, 10, 97]",
            "[72, 18, 82, 10, 97, 24]",
            "[10, 82, 18, 24, 72, 97]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[39, 40, 24, 57, 78, 21]",
        "answer": "[21, 24, 39, 40, 57, 78]",
        "choices": [
            "[21, 24, 39, 40, 57, 78]",
            "[78, 39, 57, 40, 24, 21]",
            "[39, 21, 40, 78, 24, 57]",
            "[24, 40, 39, 57, 78, 21]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[12, 84, 25, 62, 50, 68]",
        "answer": "[12, 25, 50, 62, 68, 84]",
        "choices": [
            "[12, 25, 50, 62, 68, 84]",
            "[12, 62, 68, 50, 84, 25]",
            "[25, 50, 68, 12, 84, 62]",
            "[25, 12, 68, 84, 62, 50]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[84, 13, 75, 95, 56, 40]",
        "answer": "[13, 40, 56, 75, 84, 95]",
        "choices": [
            "[13, 40, 56, 75, 84, 95]",
            "[95, 13, 84, 56, 40, 75]",
            "[40, 95, 75, 84, 56, 13]",
            "[84, 56, 13, 95, 40, 75]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[16, 31, 41, 49, 47, 77]",
        "answer": "[16, 31, 41, 47, 49, 77]",
        "choices": [
            "[16, 31, 41, 47, 49, 77]",
            "[47, 77, 41, 31, 16, 49]",
            "[41, 47, 49, 77, 31, 16]",
            "[16, 49, 31, 47, 77, 41]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[81, 46, 57, 55, 97, 58]",
        "answer": "[46, 55, 57, 58, 81, 97]",
        "choices": [
            "[46, 55, 57, 58, 81, 97]",
            "[81, 58, 55, 46, 57, 97]",
            "[57, 55, 97, 81, 58, 46]",
            "[97, 55, 81, 46, 57, 58]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[21, 94, 95, 15, 77, 13]",
        "answer": "[13, 15, 21, 77, 94, 95]",
        "choices": [
            "[13, 15, 21, 77, 94, 95]",
            "[15, 77, 13, 21, 94, 95]",
            "[15, 77, 94, 95, 13, 21]",
            "[15, 13, 95, 77, 21, 94]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[66, 27, 11, 83, 33, 54]",
        "answer": "[11, 27, 33, 54, 66, 83]",
        "choices": [
            "[11, 27, 33, 54, 66, 83]",
            "[33, 54, 83, 11, 66, 27]",
            "[11, 54, 83, 66, 33, 27]",
            "[11, 83, 54, 27, 66, 33]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[84, 13, 55, 39, 83, 47]",
        "answer": "[13, 39, 47, 55, 83, 84]",
        "choices": [
            "[13, 39, 47, 55, 83, 84]",
            "[84, 47, 55, 13, 39, 83]",
            "[83, 47, 84, 13, 55, 39]",
            "[47, 83, 55, 39, 84, 13]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[62, 40, 28, 50, 48, 44]",
        "answer": "[28, 40, 44, 48, 50, 62]",
        "choices": [
            "[28, 40, 44, 48, 50, 62]",
            "[28, 48, 62, 50, 44, 40]",
            "[48, 50, 62, 44, 28, 40]",
            "[44, 48, 40, 28, 50, 62]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[20, 41, 78, 16, 69, 72]",
        "answer": "[16, 20, 41, 69, 72, 78]",
        "choices": [
            "[16, 20, 41, 69, 72, 78]",
            "[16, 41, 78, 72, 20, 69]",
            "[20, 69, 41, 78, 72, 16]",
            "[78, 72, 16, 20, 41, 69]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[40, 74, 14, 90, 95, 26]",
        "answer": "[14, 26, 40, 74, 90, 95]",
        "choices": [
            "[14, 26, 40, 74, 90, 95]",
            "[90, 14, 74, 40, 95, 26]",
            "[40, 95, 14, 26, 74, 90]",
            "[40, 26, 90, 14, 95, 74]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[63, 47, 72, 49, 89, 70]",
        "answer": "[47, 49, 63, 70, 72, 89]",
        "choices": [
            "[47, 49, 63, 70, 72, 89]",
            "[72, 70, 63, 49, 47, 89]",
            "[89, 49, 63, 72, 47, 70]",
            "[72, 47, 49, 70, 89, 63]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[11, 93, 68, 75, 90, 60]",
        "answer": "[11, 60, 68, 75, 90, 93]",
        "choices": [
            "[11, 60, 68, 75, 90, 93]",
            "[60, 93, 68, 75, 11, 90]",
            "[75, 68, 90, 11, 93, 60]",
            "[90, 11, 75, 60, 93, 68]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[42, 93, 20, 91, 35, 22]",
        "answer": "[20, 22, 35, 42, 91, 93]",
        "choices": [
            "[20, 22, 35, 42, 91, 93]",
            "[35, 93, 42, 22, 20, 91]",
            "[35, 22, 91, 93, 42, 20]",
            "[42, 91, 20, 35, 22, 93]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[41, 65, 72, 63, 73, 76]",
        "answer": "[41, 63, 65, 72, 73, 76]",
        "choices": [
            "[41, 63, 65, 72, 73, 76]",
            "[72, 73, 65, 76, 63, 41]",
            "[76, 41, 63, 73, 72, 65]",
            "[41, 72, 65, 76, 73, 63]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[55, 29, 16, 98, 69, 58]",
        "answer": "[16, 29, 55, 58, 69, 98]",
        "choices": [
            "[16, 29, 55, 58, 69, 98]",
            "[29, 69, 98, 16, 55, 58]",
            "[55, 16, 29, 98, 69, 58]",
            "[69, 29, 58, 98, 55, 16]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[14, 94, 84, 36, 10, 85]",
        "answer": "[10, 14, 36, 84, 85, 94]",
        "choices": [
            "[10, 14, 36, 84, 85, 94]",
            "[85, 14, 84, 94, 10, 36]",
            "[85, 10, 94, 14, 84, 36]",
            "[85, 36, 84, 14, 94, 10]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[33, 50, 36, 82, 26, 84]",
        "answer": "[26, 33, 36, 50, 82, 84]",
        "choices": [
            "[26, 33, 36, 50, 82, 84]",
            "[84, 82, 33, 36, 26, 50]",
            "[36, 82, 50, 26, 33, 84]",
            "[33, 84, 50, 82, 36, 26]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[21, 17, 24, 10, 40, 84]",
        "answer": "[10, 17, 21, 24, 40, 84]",
        "choices": [
            "[10, 17, 21, 24, 40, 84]",
            "[24, 84, 10, 17, 40, 21]",
            "[40, 17, 84, 10, 24, 21]",
            "[40, 24, 84, 10, 21, 17]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[63, 53, 37, 100, 39, 90]",
        "answer": "[37, 39, 53, 63, 90, 100]",
        "choices": [
            "[37, 39, 53, 63, 90, 100]",
            "[39, 37, 53, 90, 63, 100]",
            "[39, 53, 100, 63, 37, 90]",
            "[37, 90, 39, 100, 63, 53]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[84, 66, 46, 72, 22, 39]",
        "answer": "[22, 39, 46, 66, 72, 84]",
        "choices": [
            "[22, 39, 46, 66, 72, 84]",
            "[72, 22, 66, 84, 46, 39]",
            "[72, 39, 22, 66, 46, 84]",
            "[84, 66, 22, 46, 72, 39]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[21, 49, 91, 53, 28, 30]",
        "answer": "[21, 28, 30, 49, 53, 91]",
        "choices": [
            "[21, 28, 30, 49, 53, 91]",
            "[91, 49, 53, 28, 21, 30]",
            "[91, 30, 53, 28, 49, 21]",
            "[91, 21, 28, 53, 49, 30]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[20, 38, 11, 39, 66, 13]",
        "answer": "[11, 13, 20, 38, 39, 66]",
        "choices": [
            "[11, 13, 20, 38, 39, 66]",
            "[11, 13, 66, 39, 20, 38]",
            "[20, 39, 38, 66, 11, 13]",
            "[20, 13, 38, 11, 39, 66]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[55, 25, 41, 88, 63, 54]",
        "answer": "[25, 41, 54, 55, 63, 88]",
        "choices": [
            "[25, 41, 54, 55, 63, 88]",
            "[55, 25, 54, 88, 41, 63]",
            "[88, 54, 25, 63, 41, 55]",
            "[25, 54, 55, 63, 41, 88]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[26, 50, 54, 11, 27, 68]",
        "answer": "[11, 26, 27, 50, 54, 68]",
        "choices": [
            "[11, 26, 27, 50, 54, 68]",
            "[50, 68, 54, 26, 27, 11]",
            "[27, 68, 11, 26, 50, 54]",
            "[26, 11, 27, 54, 50, 68]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[50, 13, 58, 97, 84, 37]",
        "answer": "[13, 37, 50, 58, 84, 97]",
        "choices": [
            "[13, 37, 50, 58, 84, 97]",
            "[50, 84, 97, 58, 13, 37]",
            "[37, 13, 50, 58, 84, 97]",
            "[13, 58, 84, 97, 37, 50]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[89, 73, 19, 55, 51, 60]",
        "answer": "[19, 51, 55, 60, 73, 89]",
        "choices": [
            "[19, 51, 55, 60, 73, 89]",
            "[73, 51, 55, 60, 19, 89]",
            "[73, 55, 19, 51, 89, 60]",
            "[51, 19, 60, 89, 55, 73]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[59, 82, 20, 53, 85, 79]",
        "answer": "[20, 53, 59, 79, 82, 85]",
        "choices": [
            "[20, 53, 59, 79, 82, 85]",
            "[20, 79, 85, 53, 82, 59]",
            "[85, 79, 53, 59, 82, 20]",
            "[79, 20, 59, 82, 85, 53]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[40, 59, 37, 80, 58, 51]",
        "answer": "[37, 40, 51, 58, 59, 80]",
        "choices": [
            "[37, 40, 51, 58, 59, 80]",
            "[58, 37, 51, 40, 80, 59]",
            "[40, 37, 59, 80, 58, 51]",
            "[37, 58, 40, 59, 80, 51]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[76, 79, 14, 31, 93, 19]",
        "answer": "[14, 19, 31, 76, 79, 93]",
        "choices": [
            "[14, 19, 31, 76, 79, 93]",
            "[93, 19, 76, 14, 79, 31]",
            "[79, 93, 14, 76, 19, 31]",
            "[19, 14, 93, 31, 79, 76]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[84, 32, 92, 58, 91, 74]",
        "answer": "[32, 58, 74, 84, 91, 92]",
        "choices": [
            "[32, 58, 74, 84, 91, 92]",
            "[91, 58, 32, 74, 92, 84]",
            "[91, 84, 74, 92, 58, 32]",
            "[32, 92, 91, 74, 58, 84]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[84, 95, 24, 81, 29, 67]",
        "answer": "[24, 29, 67, 81, 84, 95]",
        "choices": [
            "[24, 29, 67, 81, 84, 95]",
            "[67, 81, 95, 24, 29, 84]",
            "[84, 24, 95, 29, 67, 81]",
            "[29, 81, 84, 24, 95, 67]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[70, 48, 46, 15, 27, 71]",
        "answer": "[15, 27, 46, 48, 70, 71]",
        "choices": [
            "[15, 27, 46, 48, 70, 71]",
            "[70, 15, 71, 46, 48, 27]",
            "[27, 70, 71, 46, 15, 48]",
            "[71, 15, 46, 27, 48, 70]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[87, 41, 20, 59, 61, 50]",
        "answer": "[20, 41, 50, 59, 61, 87]",
        "choices": [
            "[20, 41, 50, 59, 61, 87]",
            "[61, 50, 59, 20, 87, 41]",
            "[59, 61, 87, 50, 41, 20]",
            "[61, 41, 59, 50, 87, 20]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[14, 54, 56, 72, 33, 96]",
        "answer": "[14, 33, 54, 56, 72, 96]",
        "choices": [
            "[14, 33, 54, 56, 72, 96]",
            "[54, 96, 72, 33, 56, 14]",
            "[72, 14, 56, 96, 54, 33]",
            "[14, 33, 54, 96, 56, 72]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[96, 16, 63, 23, 97, 42]",
        "answer": "[16, 23, 42, 63, 96, 97]",
        "choices": [
            "[16, 23, 42, 63, 96, 97]",
            "[42, 97, 63, 96, 23, 16]",
            "[16, 23, 42, 96, 63, 97]",
            "[63, 16, 42, 97, 23, 96]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[13, 91, 38, 21, 78, 41]",
        "answer": "[13, 21, 38, 41, 78, 91]",
        "choices": [
            "[13, 21, 38, 41, 78, 91]",
            "[78, 91, 21, 38, 13, 41]",
            "[91, 13, 78, 38, 41, 21]",
            "[13, 41, 78, 38, 91, 21]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[70, 98, 66, 100, 84, 81]",
        "answer": "[66, 70, 81, 84, 98, 100]",
        "choices": [
            "[66, 70, 81, 84, 98, 100]",
            "[66, 84, 100, 70, 98, 81]",
            "[81, 98, 66, 84, 70, 100]",
            "[66, 98, 100, 84, 81, 70]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[52, 14, 100, 85, 91, 57]",
        "answer": "[14, 52, 57, 85, 91, 100]",
        "choices": [
            "[14, 52, 57, 85, 91, 100]",
            "[100, 57, 52, 14, 91, 85]",
            "[14, 85, 91, 57, 52, 100]",
            "[52, 100, 91, 57, 14, 85]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[25, 57, 24, 19, 69, 94]",
        "answer": "[19, 24, 25, 57, 69, 94]",
        "choices": [
            "[19, 24, 25, 57, 69, 94]",
            "[19, 69, 24, 25, 94, 57]",
            "[25, 19, 69, 94, 24, 57]",
            "[57, 94, 19, 25, 69, 24]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[76, 58, 13, 31, 88, 82]",
        "answer": "[13, 31, 58, 76, 82, 88]",
        "choices": [
            "[13, 31, 58, 76, 82, 88]",
            "[31, 76, 88, 13, 82, 58]",
            "[58, 88, 13, 76, 82, 31]",
            "[76, 88, 58, 13, 31, 82]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[85, 50, 65, 69, 88, 92]",
        "answer": "[50, 65, 69, 85, 88, 92]",
        "choices": [
            "[50, 65, 69, 85, 88, 92]",
            "[50, 69, 92, 85, 65, 88]",
            "[50, 85, 69, 88, 65, 92]",
            "[69, 92, 88, 85, 65, 50]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[57, 56, 84, 11, 70, 79]",
        "answer": "[11, 56, 57, 70, 79, 84]",
        "choices": [
            "[11, 56, 57, 70, 79, 84]",
            "[79, 84, 11, 57, 70, 56]",
            "[57, 70, 84, 79, 11, 56]",
            "[79, 57, 11, 84, 70, 56]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[24, 72, 88, 89, 47, 23]",
        "answer": "[23, 24, 47, 72, 88, 89]",
        "choices": [
            "[23, 24, 47, 72, 88, 89]",
            "[72, 23, 24, 47, 89, 88]",
            "[23, 89, 88, 24, 47, 72]",
            "[72, 47, 24, 88, 23, 89]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[82, 58, 49, 28, 60, 54]",
        "answer": "[28, 49, 54, 58, 60, 82]",
        "choices": [
            "[28, 49, 54, 58, 60, 82]",
            "[49, 60, 82, 58, 28, 54]",
            "[58, 49, 28, 82, 60, 54]",
            "[58, 60, 54, 82, 49, 28]"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "[67, 39, 19, 45, 56, 70]",
        "answer": "[19, 39, 45, 56, 67, 70]",
        "choices": [
            "[19, 39, 45, 56, 67, 70]",
            "[56, 39, 67, 19, 70, 45]",
            "[56, 39, 67, 45, 70, 19]",
            "[67, 39, 70, 19, 56, 45]"
        ]
    }
]